const dataLevel1 = [
    {
        "id": "1",
        questionText: 'সঠিক বানান?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: 'পরিবর্তন', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'পরিবর্তণ', isCorrect: false },

        ],
        
    },
    {
        "id": "2",
        questionText: 'সঠিক বানান?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: 'স্ট্যাশনারি', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'স্ট্যাশনারী', isCorrect: false },

        ],
        
    },
    {
        "id": "3",
        questionText: 'সঠিক বানান?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: 'নিস্কাশন', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'নিষ্কাশন', isCorrect: false },

        ],

    },
    {
        "id": "4",
        questionText: 'সঠিক বানান?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: 'চীৎকার', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'চিৎকার', isCorrect: false },

        ],
       
    },
    {
        "id": "5",
        questionText: 'সঠিক বানান?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: 'অসাধারন', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'অসাধারণ', isCorrect: false },

        ],
        
    },
    {
        "id": "6",
        questionText: 'সঠিক বানান?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: '6', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'London', isCorrect: false },

        ],
        
    },
    {
        "id": "7",
        questionText: 'সঠিক বানান?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: '7', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'London', isCorrect: false },

        ],
        
    },
    {
        "id": "8",
        questionText: 'সঠিক বানান?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: '8', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'London', isCorrect: false },

        ],
        
    },
    {
        "id": "9",
        questionText: 'সঠিক বানান?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: '9', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'London', isCorrect: false },

        ],
        
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        questionText: 'সঠিক বানান?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: '10', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'London', isCorrect: false },

        ],
       }
]

export {
    dataLevel1
}